JEREMY KAN

Phone: 408-480-5177 | Website: https://jkannn.github.io/portfolio

Email: jeremykan@cpp.edu | Location: Pomona, CA

HIGHLIGHTS

Quick learner, hardworking, and team-player. Experience with coding in Java, Android-XML, SQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Proficient frontend developer with heavy interest in backend. Good understanding of software development lifecycle. Strong academic background and involvement in school (AKPsi Founding Executive Board).

EDUCATION

California State Polytechnic University, Pomona

Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems - Projected Graduation: Dec 2018, GPA: 3.67/4.0

- **Relevant Coursework:** Database Design and Development, Intermediate Java Programming for Business, Object-oriented Programming with Java, Operations Management, Financial Accounting, Managerial Accounting
- Awards: President's & Dean's List Cal Poly Pomona (2015-Present), CollegeBoard AP Scholar Award (2014, 2015)

SKILLS

- Development-platforms / languages: Android Studio, Eclipse, Microsoft Azure, Java, SQL
- Web Development languages/Tools: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Platforms: MS-Windows, Android, MacOS, Linux

WORK EXPERIENCE

Atheer Labs Mountain View, CA

SmartGlass-Android Application Developer (Intern)

June 2016 - September 2016

- Developed SmartGlass AR application for Atheer's AR Suite via custom SAP-ERP backend RESTful API integration for the following use-cases:
 - Field Service Technician scenario with SAP service transaction/notification
 - Warehouse Inspection scenario with SAP inventory/barcode data retrieval
- Independently developed the application, leading the entire software build cycle and successful deployment of the SmartGlass AR-SAP Kickstarter app on Atheer's AiRGlasses, Vuzix M100 and Recon Jet devices with an SAP ERP 6.0 EhP7 backend.
- Provided SmartGlass AR competitive marketing analysis and ROI roadmap for solution build to engineering & business development teams at Atheer

De Anza Cupertino Aquatics

Cupertino, CA

Swim Instructor

May 2013 - September 2015

 Certified Swimming Instructor having taught more than 120 students including those with disabilities as well as competitive swimmers

PROJECTS

Personal Website - https://jkannn.github.io/portfolio

- Hardcoded personal website portfolio in HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript
- Integration into GitHub

Cal Poly Pomona Chinese Student Association Website

• Utilized Scrum within the Agile framework to develop Cal Poly Pomona Chinese Student Association's website

LEADERSHIP

- Alpha Kappa Psi (largest collegiate business fraternity)
 - Historian / Marketing Committee (2016-Present) Co-founder of Colony
 - UBSS (United Business Student Senate) Representative College of Business Administration
- Management Information Systems Student Association MISSA Member
- Key Club International Vice-President (2014-2015), Director of Membership (2013-2014)